美德之光高照
Light of virtue shown
接露人之本面
Sign of one's true form
一點一滴教育
To grow, only small
引領世間萬物
Giving guidance for all
有誰能真正看懂
Seen while hardly known
九月之靛，汝之憂被淡忘
September Blue,
thy sorrows be forgotten
十月之紅，讓這季節過去
October Auburn,
let this season pass
十一之灰，以汝雨水恢復
November Gray,
restore with thy rain
十二之白，汝之美永留存
December White,
thy beauty ever last
和藹的那道晨光
Bright inviting morn
閃耀的光芒再現
Brilliant rays reborn
跟上腳步
So follow along
黑夜已成明日
as the shadows have gone
跟我穿越時空
Walk where time has torn
九月之靛，汝之憂被淡忘
September Blue,
thy sorrows be forgotten
十月之紅，讓這季節過去
October Auburn,
let this season pass
十一之灰，以汝雨水恢復
November Gray,
restore with thy rain
十二之白，汝之美永留存
December White,
thy beauty ever last
十二之白
December White
汝之美永留存
Thy beauty ever last